A Guide to the Pamela Webb Architectural Collection, 1950-2009
Special Collections, Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University
- Oversized Architectural Drawings
  - Projects
    - Borcherding Kitchen, Beaverton, OR, 1993 (Map-case 34:13:5)
    - Borkan Master Bedroom, Portland, OR, undated (Map-case 34:2:8; 34:13:6)
    - Brand Residence, Portland, OR, [1965], undated (Oversize 20:14)
    - Brantly Model Floor Plan, 1991-1992, undated (Oversize 20:15)
    - Bridgeview Meeting Center, Portland, OR, 1997 (Oversize 20:16)
    - Bullseye House, 1993, undated (Oversize 20:17)
    - Cable Village, Portland, OR, 1994-1995, undated (Oversize 20:18-20; 21:1,, Map-case 34:2:9-14; 34:13:7,, Oversize 39-40)
    - Century 21 Hearthside [Tanasbourne Village], 1990-1993 (Map-case 34:2:15-16)
    - Charbonneau [AKA French Prairie], Wilsonville, OR, undated (Oversize 21:2)
    - Chown Showroom, Portland, OR, 1997 (Oversize 21:3,, Map-case 34:2:17; 34:13:8)
    - Christiansen Addition, Portland, OR, 1994, undated (Oversize 21:4-5)
    - Christy Renovation [variously spelled Christie], Portland, OR, 1998-1999, undated (Oversize 21:6-7,, Map-case 34:2:18)
    - Ciranny House, Portland, OR, 1994, undated (Oversize 21:8,, Map-case 34:3:1)
    - Claremont Clubhouse [Claremont Country Club], Portland, OR 1991, undated (Oversize 21:9-10,, Map-case 34:3:2-3; 34:13:9)
    - Cody Garden Room and Big Garage, Portland, OR, 1995, undated (Oversize 21:11)
    - Cogan Residence, Portland, OR, 1984-1985, 1992 (Oversize 21-12-13,, Map-case 34:3:4)
    - Cogan / Neidig Flood Repairs, Portland, OR, 1992, 1996, undated (Oversize 21:14)
    - Constant Improvements, Portland, OR, 1995, undated (Oversize 21:15)
    - County Cork Public House, Portland, OR, 1999 (Oversize 22:1-2)
    - Cultural Campus, undated (Map-case 34:3:5)
    - Curtis Project, undated (Oversize 22:3)
    - Cutler House, 1999, undated (Oversize 22:4)
    - Danielson Attic Renovation, 1984 (Map-case 34:3:6)
    - Darmohray Renovations, Portland, OR, undated, c. 1998 (Map-case 34:3:7)
    - Darney Project, undated (Oversize 22:5,, Oversize 41)
    - Davis Remodel, Portland, OR, 1986 (Map-case 34:3:8-9; 34:13:10)
    - Du Charme Project, undated (Oversize 22:6)
    - Eastbank [Three Buildings for...], Portland, OR undated (Oversize 22:7-8,, Map-case 34:3:10)
    - Eastbank [for "Downtowner"], Portland, OR, undated, c. 1992 (Map-case 34:3:11; 34:13:11)
    - Eastbank Master Plan, Portland, OR, 1992 (Oversize 22:9,, Oversize 42-43)
    - Eliot Row—Forest Heights, Portland, OR, 1989, 1991, undated (Oversize 22:10)
    - Epstein Project, Portland, OR, [1989], 2001, undated (Oversize 22:11-12)
    - Ettinger Apartment, 2003 (Oversize 22:13)
    - Ettinger Beach House, Lincoln City, OR, 1990-1991, 1995, undated (Oversize 22:14-15,, Map-case 34:3:12)
    - Faherty Renovations, Beaverton, OR, 1997, undated (Oversize 22:16-17)
    - Frazier Court, Portland, OR, undated (Map-case 34:3:13-15)
    - Forest Heights, Portland, OR, 1991-1992, undated (Oversize 22:18-19,, Oversize 44)
    - Forest Heights—ARC Site Visit Maps, Portland, OR, 1992 (Oversize 22:20)
    - Forest Heights—Miscellaneous Design, Portland, OR, 1992, undated (Oversize 22-21)
    - Free Project, undated (Oversize 22:22)
    - Frohnmayer Residence, Portland, OR, undated (Map-case 34:3:16)
    - Frohnmayer Kitchen, Portland, OR, 1981 (Oversize 22:23)
    - Gateway Plaza Apartments, Beaverton, OR, 2001 (Oversize 22:24)
    - Gentlemann Alt. Elevations, 1991, undated (Oversize 23:1)
    - Glick / Kaplan Kitchen Renovation, Portland, OR 1998, undated (Frame 23:2)
    - Goldschmidt Office, Portland, OR, 1993 (Oversize 23:3)
    - Gordon Beach House, Surf Pines, OR, 2000-2003, 2006, undated (Oversize 23:4-10,, Map-case 34:3:17-18; 34:4:1)
    - Gordon House, Portland, OR, 2008, undated (Oversize 23:11)
    - Gordon Kitchen, Portland, OR, [1998], 2006 (Oversize 23:12)
    - Gordon—Unlabled Sketches, undated (Oversize 23:13)
      May go with either the Gordon Residence in Portland or the Beach House in Surf Pines.
    - Green / Holden Project, Portland, OR, 1984, undated (Oversize 23:14,, Map-case 34:4:2-3)
    - Greenberg / Ritchie, Portland, OR, 2000, 2001, undated (Oversize 23:15-20; 24:1,, Map-case 34:4:4)
    - Greene Project, Seattle, WA, 1997, undated (Oversize 24:2,, Map-case 34:4:5)
    - Greenfield Health System, Portland, OR, 2001, undated (Oversize 24:3,, Map-case 34:4:6)
    - Gregg Kitchen Renovation, Portland, OR, 1991, undated (Oversize 24:4,, Map-case 34:4:7; 34:14:1)
    - Gresham Row, undated (Oversize 24:5)
    - Griffith / Dickey Remodel, Portland, OR, 1992, 1994, undated (Oversize 24:6-12,, Map-case 34:4:8-9)
    - Griffith / Dickey House II, Portland, OR, undated (Oversize 24:13)
    - Hall Farmhouse Renovation, Troutdale, OR, 1996 (Map-case 34:4:10-12)
    - Hansen Renovations, Portland, OR, 1992, 1995, undated (Oversize 24:14)
    - Hartford House, undated (Map-case 34:14:2)
    - Havurah Shalom, Portland, OR, 1996-1999 (Oversize 24:15; 25:1,, Map-case 34:4:13-16; 34:5:1)
    - Hearing / Lawshe Remodel, Portland, OR, 1992-1993, undated (Frame 25:2-9,, Map-case 34:5:2)
    - Hendrix / Streb House, Portland, OR, 2002-2004, undated (Oversize 25:10-12)
    - Holmes Project, Portland, OR, [1950],1999-2000 (Oversize 25:13,, Map-case 34:5:3-4)
    - Hotel Design Group Project, undated (Map-case 34:5:5)
    - Hurst / Bonini Kitchen, Portland, OR, 1986, undated (Oversize 25:14,, Map-case 34:5:6; 34:14:3,, Oversize 45)
    - Illiinski House, Portland, OR, undated (Oversize 26:1)
    - Ingersoll / Dayton Residential Remodel, Portland, OR, 1989, undated (Oversize 26:2-3)
    - Inner Sound, Portland, OR, 2000, undated (Oversize 26:4)
    - Jacobs Residence, Portland, OR, undated (Oversize 26:5)
    - Johnson County House, West Linn, OR, 2000, undated (Oversize 26:6,, Map-case 34:5:7-8; 34:14:4)
    - Johnson / Wilson Addition, Portland, OR, undated (Map-case 34:5:9-10)
    - Kah-nee-ta Village, Warm Springs, OR, 1998 (Oversize 26:7)
    - Kalisvaart & Co., Portland, OR, 1995, undated (Oversize 26:8-9)
    - Kalisvaart & Co. Apartment Building, Portland, OR, 1996 (Oversize 26:10)
    - Kaye Cabin, Hood River, OR, 1991, undated (Oversize 26:11,, Map-case 34:5:11-12)
    - Kilston Home, Cottage Grove, OR, 1998 (Map-case 34:5:11-13)
    - Kirsch Project [on Greenhills], Portland, OR, undated, c. 2001 (Map-case 34:5:14)
    - Klapper / Hickey Attick #2, Portland, OR, 1987 (Map-case 34:5:15-17)
    - Klapper / Hickey Cabin Renovations, Bend, OR, 2000 (Map-case 34:5:18)
    - Klapper / Hickey Kitchen, Portland, OR, 1981, 2000, undated (Oversize 26:12-16)
    - Koop House, Portland, OR, 1991 (Oversize 18:5; 26:17,, Map-case 34:5:19-20; 34:6:1-3; 34:14:5-6)
    - Krener Project, undated, c. 1995 (Oversize 26:18)
    - Kuhn Farmhouse Expansion, Silverton, OR, 1991 (Oversize 26:19)
    - Lake Grove Commercial Center, Lake Grove, OR, [1979], undated (Oversize 26:20,, Map-case 34:6:4)
    - Langford House, Portland, OR, 1992-1993, undated (Oversize 18:6; 26:21-24,, Map-case 34:6:5-9; 34:14:7)
    - Lansky Project, 1999, undated (Oversize 26:25)
    - Legacy Homes [Also known as Carr Custom Homes], 1985-1986, undated (Oversize 26:26,, Map-case 34:6:10; 34:7:1-6; 34:14:8-9)
    - Leland Project, undated (Oversize 26:27)
    - Levy / Maranze Remodel [Garage], Portland, OR, 1991, undated (Oversize 26:28,, Map-case 34:7:7; 34:14:10)
    - Lewis County Center For Civic Activities and Performing Arts, Lewis County, OR, 1990 (Oversize 27:1)
    - Lincoln Loan, 1986, undated (Oversize 27:2-3,, Map-case 34:7:8)
    - Lipsitz-Basin Kitchen Remodel, Portland, OR, 2006, undated (Oversize 27:4)
    - Lipsitz-Basin Remodel, Portland, OR, 1996 (Map-case 34:7:9)
    - Mahoney Addition, Sherwood, OR, 1995 (Oversize 27:5)
    - Mahoney Residence, Lake Oswego, OR, 1997 (Map-case 34:7:10)
    - Mangan at Forest Heights, Portland, OR, undated (Oversize 27:6)
    - Margolin Project, Portland, OR, 1995, undated (Oversize 27:7,, Map-case 34:7:11-12)
    - Margolin Vacation Home, 2006, undated (Oversize 27:8)
    - Marian Abram's Children's Wing [MJCC], Portland, OR, [1969], 1994-1995 (Oversize 27:9-10,, Map-case 34:7:13-17; 34:15:1-2)
    - McCarron Residence, Portland, OR, 1979 (Oversize 27:11)
    - McTink [McCoy / Tinkle], Fairview, OR, 1999, undated (Oversize 27:12-13,, Map-case 34:7:18)
    - Meadowlark Condominiums, Aloha, OR, [1978], 1999-2002, undated (Oversize 18:7; 27:14-18,, Map-case 34:7:19-22; 34:8:1; 34:15:3,, Oversize 46)
    - Miller Addition, Portland, OR, 1999-2000, undated (Oversize 27:19)
    - Mistral De Province, Hillsboro, OR, 1997, undated (Oversize 27:20)
    - Mittleman Jewish Community Center, Portland, OR, [1983], 1986, 1991, 1994-1996, undated (Oversize 28:1-4,, Map-case 34:8:2; 34:15:4)
    - Morgan Deck, Portland, OR, undated (Map-case 34:8:3)
    - Morgan Kitchen, Portland, OR, 1985-1986 (Map-case 34:8:4; 34:15:5)
    - Morgan Renovations, Portland, OR, [1986], 1998, undated (Oversize 28:5)
    - Moskovitz Tenant Improvements, Portland, OR, 2000 (Map-case 34:8:5)
    - Mowe Kitchen, Portland, OR, 1986 (Frame 29:6-7, Map-case 34:8:6)
    - Mowe Project, 1980 (Oversize 28:8)
    - Mowe Westmoreland House, Portland, OR, 2002, 2003, undated (Oversize 28:9-12)
    - Murray Hill Coffee Co., Beaverton, OR, 1991-1992 (Map-case 34:8:7)
    - Murray Hill Expo, Beaverton, OR, undated (Map-case 34:8:8-9)
    - Murray Hill Eye Care, Beaverton, OR, 1992, undated (Oversize 28:13-16, Map-case 34:8:8-10)
    - "Mystery House #2," undated (Map-case 34:8:11)
    - Nachtigal Residence, Portland, OR, 1993, undated (Oversize 28:17,, Map-case 34:8:12-13)
    - Naito Project, undated (Oversize 28:18)
    - Nakayama Garage, Portland, OR, undated (Map-case 34:8:14-15)
    - NIA Child Center, Portland, OR, undated (Oversize 28:19)
    - Newhall Farmhouse, Sauvie Island, OR, 1988 (Map-case 34:8:16-18; 34:15:6)
    - Northwest Artists Workshop—"Completing the Square," 1983 (Map-case 34:8:19)
    - Oregon Hydrocarbon, Portland, OR, undated, c. 1991 (Map-case 34:8:20)
    - Oregon Symphony Orchestra [Tenant Improvements], Portland, OR, 1991, undated (Oversize 28:20)
    - OSU Great Hall, Corvallis, OR, 1979 (Oversize 28:21)
    - Pacwest Center, Portland, OR, 1983-1984 (Oversize 28:22)
    - Pakman Cleaners, Portland, OR, 1993-1995, undated (Oversize 28:23,, Map-case 34:8:21; 34:15:7)
    - Parcel "E," 1991, undated (Oversize 28:24)
    - Parker House, Portland, OR, undated (Oversize 29:1)
    - Peterson Keating House, Portland, OR, 1992 (Oversize 29:2)
    - Pinnacle Court, undated (Oversize 29:3)
    - Plowman Residence, Beaverton, OR, 1986 (Map-case 34:8:22)
    - Porter Renovation, Portland, OR, 1993 (Oversize 29:4)
    - Portis Renovations, Portland, OR, 1999 (Oversize 29:5,, Map-case 34:8:23)
    - Portland Jewish Academy, Portland, OR, 1995 (Map-case 34:8:24-5)
    - Portland Trolleycar Lofts, Portland, OR, 1996 (Map-case 34:8:26)
    - Premier Press, Portland, OR, 1998 (Oversize 29:6-7)
    - Price Kitchen Remodel, Portland, OR, 1991 (Map-case 34:9:1)
    - Prince Residence, Portland, OR, undated (Oversize 29:8)
    - Pyramid Storage, 1989, undated (Oversize 29:9,, Map-case 34:9:2; 34:15:8)
    - Quintana Project, undated (Oversize 29:10)
    - Rackner / Wolf Project, 1997, undated (Oversize 29:11,, Map-case 34:9:3)
    - Raphael Renovations, Portland, OR (Oversize 29:12-14)
    - Raske Project (as built), Portland, OR, 1983 (Map-case 34:15:9)
    - Reich Remodel, 1991, undated (Oversize 29:15-16,, Map-case 34:9:4-5)
    - Reid House, Portland, OR, 1990, 1991 (Oversize 29:17,, Map-case 34:9:6-7)
    - Rhine Project, Portland, OR, [1964], undated, c. 1991 (Map-case 34:9:8; 34:15:10)
    - Riddle Renovation, Portland, OR, 1998 (Map-case 34:9:9)
    - River Front at Lake Oswego, Lake Oswego, OR, 1987 (Oversize 29:18)
    - Rizley / Brown Sauna-Sunroom, undated (Oversize 29:19)
    - Rock Creek Cleaners at Tanasbourne Village, 1993 (Oversize 29:20)
    - Rosenberg Renovations, Portland, OR, 1998, undated (Oversize 29:21,, Map-case 34:9:10)
    - Rosenberg / Anderson Project, Portland, OR, 1998, undated (Oversize 29:22,, Map-case 34:9:11)
    - Rosenberg / Lippman Project, Portland, OR, 1996, undated (Oversize 29:23-28,, Map-case 34:9:12-13)
    - Rosenthall Project, 2004 (Oversize 29:29-30)
    - Rystadt Apartments [Goose Hollow Neighbourhood] also referred to as Cathedral Park Condos, Portland, OR, 2001 (Oversize 30:1,, Map-case 34:9:14)
    - Saint John Parker Entrance Design, Portland, OR, 1991 (Map-case 34:9:15-16)
    - Sargo's Plumbing, Lake Oswego, OR, 2005, undated (Oversize 30:2)
    - Satir / Fuson Project, undated (Oversize 30:3)
    - Schultz Residence, 2002 (Oversize 30:4-5)
    - Schweber Kitchen Remodel, Portland, OR. 2001 (Oversize 30:6)
    - Schwoerer Residence, Portland, OR, 1992-1993 (Oversize 30:7-8,, Map-case 34:9:17-18,, Oversize 47)
    - Seiss / Sanchez Renovation, Portland, OR, 1999 (Oversize 30:9)
    - Skloot Kitchen, Portland, OR, undated (Oversize 30:10, Map-case 34:9:19)
    - Skyline Summit [Early Designs], Portland, OR, undated, c. 1993 (Map-case 34:9:20-22; 34:15:11)
    - Skyline Summit, Portland, OR, 1998, 1993, 1995, undated (Oversize 30:11,, Map-case 34:9:23-25; 34:10:1; 34:15:12-13)
    - Springridge [Poolhouse, Golf Cart Storage], Wilsonville, OR, 1991, 1992 (Oversize 30:12,, Map-case 34:10:2; 34:15:14)
    - Stan, Small House For..., undated (Oversize 30:13)
    - Stenzel Beach Cottage, Barview, OR, undated (Map-case 34:10:3)
    - Steward House, 1992 (Map-case 34:10:4-5)
    - Stone / Moreland, Portland, OR, 1998 (Oversize 30:14)
    - Sukkot Project, Portland, OR, undated (Oversize 30:15)
    - Taste of China, Lake Oswego, OR, 1992 (Oversize 30:16-18,, Map-case 34:10:6-8)
    - Theater on the Park, 1984 (Map-case 34:10:9)
    - Thomas Residential Addition, Newberg, OR, 2001 (Oversize 30:19,, Map-case 34:10:10; 34:15:15)
    - Tinning Property, 2000 (Map-case 34:10:11)
    - Torson Residence, Portland, OR, 1982 (Map-case 34:10:12-13)
    - Tuality Christian Center, Aloha, OR, 1996 (Oversize 31:1)
    - Two Barns Farm, Yamhill County, OR, 1998 (Oversize 31:2,, Map-case 34:10:14-15)
    - Verity Homes [Empty Nest], 1992 (Oversize 31:3-4,, Map-case 34:11:1-3)
    - Veron Houseboat, Portland, OR, undated, c. 1991 (Oversize 18:8; 31:5-6,, Map-case 34:11:4)
    - Vranizan Attic Renovations, Portland, OR, 1991, undated (Oversize 31:7,, Map-case 34:11:5-6)
    - Warm Springs—Fast Food / Community Mall Master Plan, Warm Springs, OR, 1992 (Map-case 34:11:7)
    - Warm Springs—Miscellaneous Drawings, Warm Springs, OR, undated (Oversize 31:8)
    - Warm Springs Restaurant, Warm Springs, OR, 1992, undated (Oversize 31:9,, Map-case 34:11:8-10)
    - Warm Springs--Topographic Surveys/Maps, Warm Springs, OR, undated (Map-case 34:15:16,, Oversize 48)
    - Wax Urban Arts Center, Portland, OR, 2004, undated (Map-case 34:11:11)
    - Webb Renovations, Florida, 1996 (Map-case 34:11:12-13)
    - Webb / Margulies Renovations, Portland, OR, undated, c. 1987 (Oversize 31:13)
    - Weisburg / Webb Project, Portland, OR, [1965], 1994 (Oversize 31:14, Map-case 34:11:14)
    - West Residence, Portland, OR, 2004 (Oversize 31:15-16)
    - West Village Construction, undated (Oversize 31:17-18)
    - Whitney Renovations, Portland, OR, 1995-1996 (Oversize 31:19)
    - Willamette Print and Blueprint Co., Portland, OR, 1995 (Oversize 31:20,, Map-case 34:11:15-19)
    - Willis Garage / Carport, 1996 (Map-case 34:11:20)
    - Wotipka Project, Portland, OR, 2000 (Oversize 31:21)